export const android_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is Android?",
    answer: "Android is an open-source Software package and Linux-based operating system used in mobiles, tablets, televisions, etc. The Mobile OS is own by Search giant Google. However, the system is open source, so it is freely accessible to anyone.",
  },
  {
    question: "What programming language do you use to develop Android apps?",
    answer: "We use Java and Kotlin programming languages to develop native Android apps. While for cross-platform app development, we use React Native and Flutter programming languages.    ",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the benefits of outsourcing Android App Development?",
    answer: "Here are some of the most important benefits of outsourcing your Android App development:",
    answer1: "Low development and operational cost",
    answer2: " Access to experienced developers",
    answer3: " Reducing the Risk Factors",
    answer4: " Reduced development times",
    answer5: " Access to experienced developers",
    answer6: " High Speed of Development",
    answer7: " Ongoing Support",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost to develop an Android App?",
    answer: "The cost of any Mobile App Development depends on various factors such as the complexity of application, Platform Used for Development, features you need in your app, Time required for development, etc.  So, it is very difficult to determine an exact cost to develop an Android App. To get a proper insight and estimate cost of your Android Application, get in touch with our App developers at:   ",
  },
  {
    question: "What do you mean by Google Android SDK?",
    answer: "The Google Android SDK is the software development Kit for android application. It provides a set of libraries and other resources which helps in the android app development. The Android SDK contains all the tools and libraries which is necessary to code programs from scratch and even test them.    ",
  },
  {
    question: "How we can avoid the ANR Situation?",
    answer: "ANR stands for Application Not Responding. The message is displayed to the user when a long operation takes place in the UI thread and the application is not responding for the longest time. To avoid the ANR Situation, Stop doing heavy jobs on main thread. Instead use worker threads such as Intent Service, Async Task or another Thread. ",
  },
  {
    question: "What Kind of Android Apps Developed by Ftechiz?",
    answer: "We develop a large variety of apps ranging from Healthcare, entertainment, travel, social networking, productivity, Blockchain, business, Education and many more.",
  },
];
export const blockchain_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is Blockchain Technology?",
    answer: "Blockchain Technology is an innovative system of storing information or data in such a way that makes it difficult or impossible to alter or hack. It’s called a blockchain because, in reality, it is duplicated and distributed across the entire network of computer systems on the blockchain. Once a data is stored on a blockchain technology, it is extremely difficult to change or alter it. Each transaction on a blockchain technology is secured with a digital signature that proves its authenticity. The information stored on the blockchain technology is tamper-proof and cannot be changed.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the benefits of Blockchain Development?",
    answer: "There are many benefits of blockchain technology. Some of them are listed below: \n* Low Cost of Operation \n* No Single Point of Failure \n* Improved Security & Confidentiality \n* Faster Transactions \n* Reduces Fraud \n* Transparent & Universal Recording System ",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost for Blockchain App Development?",
    answer: "The cost of blockchain app development depends on various factors such as the complexity of application, features of the app, industry compliances, technology used, time duration, etc. So, it is very tough to determine an exact cost to develop a Blockchain App.  It is recommended to consult an blockchain development company to get proper insight. To get an estimate cost, get in touch with our App developers at: <b>business@ftechiz.com</b>",
  },
  {
    question: "What Are Blockchain Development Services Provided by Ftechiz?",
    answer: "Below is the list of Blockchain Development Services offered by Ftechiz: \n * Smart Contract Development \n* Blockchain Application Development \n* Fintech Application Development \n* Crypto Wallet Development \n* Supply chain management using Blockchain Technology \n* Blockchain Consulting",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the Technologies used by Ftechiz for Blockchain Development?",
    answer: "Below is the list of Technology Stack used by Ftechiz for Blockchain Development: \n* Hyperledger \n* Ethereum \n* Stellar \n* Corda \n* EOS \n* Tron \n* Hashgraph",
  },
  {
    question: "Why Ftechiz is the right choice for Blockchain Development?",
    answer: "There are numerous reasons why businesses are choosing Ftechiz for Blockchain Development. The reasons usually vary from our Blockchain Development services, Experience Developers, Industry Experience, Client Satisfaction and latest technology stacks. We have successfully delivered more than 20+ projects in the various industry verticals.",
  },
];

export const cloud_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is a Cloud based Applications?",
    answer: "A cloud-based application simply refers to any software application that is deployed in a cloud environment rather than being hosted on a local server or workstation.",
  },
  {
    question: "Is cloud computing same as Software as a Service (SAAS)?",
    answer: "Software as a Service (SAAS) is termed as one of the several components of cloud computing. As SAAS pushed cloud computing by demonstrating that IT services can be simply created accessible over the internet.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can we move applications from one cloud to another?",
    answer: "Yes, applications can be moved from one cloud to another but it may not be easy task to do so. Adopting a standard technology in order to ensure interoperability is one method that cloud vendors can use.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the Cloud-Based Development Services offered by Ftechiz?",
    answer: "We offer a wide range of Cloud-Based Development Services that are Secure, Reliable, and Cost-Effective and help you to Transform Your Business. Here are some of the Cloud Development Services we offer: \n* Cloud Migration Services \n* Cloud Computing Architecture \n* Cloud Document Verification \n* Cloud Backup Solutions",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the Technologies used by Ftechiz for Cloud Application Development?",
    answer: "Here is the list of Cloud Computing Tech used by Ftechiz for Cloud Application Development: \n * Amazon Web Services: Amazon EC2, Amazon Dynamo DB, Amazon Route 53, Amazon API Gateway, Amazon RDS, AWS IoT, AWS Cloud Formation \n * Google Cloud: Cloud Run, Cloud Storage, Compute Engine, App Engine, Cloud SDK, Cloud SQL, Google Kubernetes Engine \n * Microsoft Azure: Azure AKS, Azure Logic Apps, Azure Functions, Azure CDN, Azure Load Balancer, Azure IoT, Azure Data Lake",
  },
  {
    question: "Why is cloud computing the future of modern technology?",
    answer: "The Future of Technology is said to be highly competitive and requires agile technologies to sustain in the long run. You can save your business money on servers and management services, data storage and processing by using Cloud computing. By moving these resources on the cloud at the minimal cost, you save your time and money while making your operations more efficient.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between web application and cloud application?",
    answer: "The major difference between web applications and cloud applications is their architecture. A web-based application required a continuous internet connection to function properly. On the other hand, a cloud-based application can temporarily perform their processing tasks on a local computer or workstation.",
  },
];
export const flutter_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is a Flutter app development?",
    answer: "Flutter is Google’s open-source framework for creating high-performing, flexible and interactive mobile apps for iOS, Android, Web and Desktop platforms. Flutter is written in Dart language, uses a single codebase and compiles it into native code for mobile, desktop and web platforms.",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost in Flutter app development?",
    answer: "The cost of Flutter App Development depends on various factors such as the complexity of application, features you need in your app, Time required for development, etc.  So, it is very difficult to determine an exact cost to develop a Flutter App. To get a proper insight and estimate cost of your Flutter Application, get in touch with our App developers at:",
  },
  {
    question: "What types of apps can you make with Flutter?",
    answer: "Flutter is a full-fledged open-source SDK created by Google. We can develop all types of apps using the latest hardware and software features like geo-location, camera, etc., with Flutter, for any store categories for both Android and iOS Platforms.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why Should I choose Ftechiz Solutions over other Flutter App Development companies?",
    answer: "There are various reasons why businesses are choosing Ftechiz for Flutter App Development. The reasons usually vary from our Flutter App Development services, Experience Developers, Industry Experience, on-time delivery, Client Satisfaction and latest technology stacks.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why we choose Flutter for App Development?",
    answer: "Since it's an open-source mobile application development framework, developed and maintained by Google, it provides safer, flexibility and quick development with the simplest development expertise for both Android and iOS Platforms.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the general Flutter App Development process you follow?",
    answer: "We follow the following Flutter app development process: \n* Requirement Gathering \n* UI/UX Designing \n* Development \n* Testing \n* Deployment \n* Support and Maintenance",
  },
];
export const ios_ques = [
  {
    question: "What programming language do you use to develop iOS apps?",
    answer: "We use Objective C, Python and Swift programming language to develop native iOS apps. Normally for iOS app development we use Swift Language because of its faster development quality. We use React Native and Flutter for cross-platform IOS app development.",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost to build an IOS app?",
    answer: "The cost of IOS App Development depends on various factors such as the complexity of application, Platform Used for Development, features you need in your app, Time required for development, etc.  So, it is very difficult to determine an exact cost to develop an IOS App. To get a proper insight and estimate cost of your IOS Application, get in touch with our App developers at:",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Services are offered by Ftechiz Solutions?",
    answer: "We create iOS app using both native and cross-platform application development approaches. We work on the entire IOS App development cycle, from concept to deployment. We deliver end-to-end custom products that cover the complete range of iOS devices, including iPhone, iPad, apple watch, and tv app development.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why Should I choose Ftechiz Solutions over other iOS Application Development companies?",
    answer: "There are various reasons why businesses are choosing Ftechiz for IOS App Development. The reasons usually vary from ourIOS Development services, Experience Developers, Industry Experience, Client Satisfaction and latest technology stacks. We have successfully delivered projects in the various industry verticals.",
  },
  {
    question: "Is it possible to develop an IOS app in just one month?",
    answer: "No, it is not possible to develop a complete IOS app in just one month. The time required for development totally depends upon the requirements of your project. To get a proper insight, get in touch with our App developers at:",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the general IOS App Development process you follow?",
    answer: "We follow the following IOS app development process: \n* Gather & Analyzing Requirements \n* Designing & Development \n* Testing & Deployment \n* Support and Maintenance",
  },
  {
    question: "How can you handle my Security Concerns?",
    answer: "We have a team of Experienced Developers which follows proper encryption and the latest data security techniques while building an app to make highly-secure apps. The apps developed by us are highly secure.",
  },
];
export const mobile_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is Mobile App Development?",
    answer: "Mobile app development is the process of creating software applications (Apps) that run on a mobile device (phones, tablets, etc.).",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it Cost to develop a mobile app?",
    answer: "The cost of any Mobile App Development depends on various factors such as the complexity of application, features of the app, Platform Used (IOS, Android), technology used, time duration, etc. So, it is very tough to determine an exact cost to develop a Mobile App. It is recommended to consult an app development company to get proper insight. To get an estimate cost of your Mobile Application, get in touch with our App developers at:",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the benefits of outsourcing mobile app development services?",
    answer: "Here are some of the most important benefits of outsourcing your mobile app development: * Low development and operational cost * Reducing the Risk Factors * Reduced development times * Access to experienced developers * High Speed of Development",
  },
  {
    question: "How much time would it take for the App to develop?",
    answer: "The time required to develop a mobile application is depends on the complexity of the application. While it usually can range from 6 months to a year to finish the app development process straight from ideation to launch, depending on features of the application that client wants to add.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can you Build Apps for both IOS and Android?",
    answer: "Yes, most of the apps developed by us support both iOS and Android mobile platforms. We work on both native and cross-platform mobile app development. It’s common, everyone wants their applications to work on both web and mobile devices, so we use both Native and Cross-Platform Technologies such as React, react native, Flutter, Xmarin, and so on that enable us to quickly support both platforms.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the different types of mobile apps you can develop?",
    answer: "We build mobile apps of all platforms (Android, iOS, Window) including Native Apps development, Hybrid apps, Mobile-Web Apps, and cross-platform apps development. We use all the latest technologies to develop all the apps.",
  },
  {
    question: "What Kind of Apps Developed by Ftechiz?",
    answer: "We develop a wide variety of apps ranging from utilities, entertainment, travel, finance, social networking, productivity, weather, business, Education and children's apps.",
  },
];
export const reactnative_ques = [
  {
    question: "Why should we choose Ftehciz for React Native App development?",
    answer: "There are different reasons why businesses are choosing Ftechiz for React Native App Development. The reasons usually vary from our React Native App Development services, Industry Experience, Categories Served, Cost-effective Solutions, Client Satisfaction and latest technology stacks.",
  },
  {
    question: "Is React Native good for app development?",
    answer: "Yes, developing a mobile app using the react native technology is definitely a good step. Using React Native, developers can make applications that operate faster than the usual speed and it will work perfectly for Android & iOS Platforms.",
  },
  {
    question: "How long will it take to develop a React Native app?",
    answer: "It totally depends on the size of your React Native development project and the design, features and purpose of the app. For more detailed information and free consultation, please reach out via email or call and we will get back to you.",
  },
  {
    question: "What after-sales services do you offer?",
    answer: "We support each website or application we create using React Native, and are always available in case you discover any issues or need any update to your mobile application. Ftechiz offers full support and maintenance services.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you take responsibility for the security of the app?",
    answer: "Yes, we do. We make sure that your application is totally secure by executing the most recent security features. We put the application through a rigorous testing stage to make sure that it is safe for you and your clients to use.",
  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer: "We follow the following React-Native app development process: * Information Gathering & Planning * UI/UX Designing * App Development * QA & Testing * App Launch * Support and Maintenance",
  },
];
export const webapp_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is Web Application Development?",
    answer: "Web application development is the process of designing, building, testing and deploying a web-based application. It will be installed on remote servers and once a web application has been deployed on an application server then users can access the application and its functions and services using any web browser.",
  },
  {
    question: "How long does it take to develop a Web Application?",
    answer: "The time required to develop a web application is depends on the complexity of the application. While it usually can range from 6 months to a year to finish the web app development process straight from ideation to launch, depending on features and functionality of the application that client wants to add.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the web app development services provide by Ftechiz?",
    answer: "Following are some of the web app development company services provided by Ftechiz:",

    answer1: "Custom application development: If you want to build a custom web app from scratch, migrate your legacy backend, or streamline existing front-end functionality, we can achieve that in an efficient and cost-effective manner. We offer business intelligence solutions, application migration to cloud, collaboration and portal development, document management solutions, offer maintenance, support, and up-gradation.",
     
    
    answer2: "Portal development: We can also help create agile and advanced customer, business self-service, and other business web portals. We always make sure that all the boxes are checked for usability parameters such as easy navigation, quick response time, higher credibility, better reliability, and high-quality content for your B2B and B2C portals.",
     
    
    answer3: "E-Commerce development: We also provide end-to-end ecommerce solutions with payment gateway integration, plug-in high-end modules, round-the-clock maintenance, and appealing UX for a pleasant experience to the end users.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the Technologies used by Ftechiz for Web Application Development?",
    answer: "Below is the list of Technology Stack used by Ftechiz for Web Application Development? * JS * Ajax * js * Java * PHP * Laravel * net * React JS * CodeIgniter",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost for Web application Development?",
    answer: "The cost of web application development depends on various factors like its features, complexity, development time, technology stack used, and level of customization. So, it is very tough to determine an exact cost to develop a Web Application. If you have any requirements, please share them with us and Get a free consultation from our Web App developers at:",
  },
  {
    question: "Should I have website with all features same as application?",
    answer: "It is not compulsory to have a website with same features as web application. You can target web app development first with one-page website. After getting more traction, you can develop responsive website with same feature as your application.",
  },
];
export const webdesigning_ques = [
  {
    question: "Why do I need website design?",
    answer: "Do you know? In the current digital age, more than 80% of the businesses have an online presence. So your website should get an edge over your other competitors. So, there is clearly a need of an amazing design for your website. Design defines the story of your business when it is online. So without hesitating more, ping us to know what the classy website design company has in store for you!",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you redesign existing websites?",
    answer: "Yes we do. Make sure your reasons for reasons for redesigning are valid before approaching for website redesign. From your ROI point of view this will ensure the project is an overall success.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I See My Website Design While It's In Progress?",
    answer: "Definitely! We always keep our clients in the loop. Our team builds your website on the server and gives you with login credentials so that you can keep an eye on the ongoing progress. We also encourage our clients to give us regular feedback as it helps us make the changes per your requirement.",
  },
  {
    question: "What if I need some changes in the website after the development process is complete?",
    answer: "Depending on the type of changes you need in your website or the service package you choose; our dedicated team members answer all of your queries and support you accordingly. Furthermore, if you need any changes when the designing process is still on or till the website hasn’t been launched, then just get in touch with our development team directly for the same.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why to Choose Ftechiz for web designing Services?",
    answer: "Ftechiz is one of the leading web design companies, with the highest customer retention rate. There are various reasons why industries are choosing Ftechiz for Web Designing. The reasons usually vary from our Website Designing services, Highly Skilled Designers, Industry Experience, Cost Effective Solutions, Client Satisfaction, latest tools and technology stacks.",
  },
];
export const webdevelopment_ques = [
  {
    question: "Do I Really Need A Website For My Business?",
    answer: "As technology has become more advanced in the digital age, consumer behavior has also evolved throughout time. Therefore, in this digital world you need to be found online, which implies that you need to have a website, if you want to expand your business.",
  },
  {
    question: "How long does it take to develop a Website?",
    answer: "A good website can take 2-3 months to complete from design to development which includes 1 week of planning and requirement gathering, 2 weeks designing phase, 3 weeks of development phase, and 2 weeks of modifications and testing. It can take more or less time depending on your website requirement, features, budget and complexity.",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does website development cost?",
    answer: "There is no one exact answer to this question. It totally depends on a range of factors like complexity, technology integration, number of features, number of devices, time required, it will be made live in, and scope of scalability. The more/less they are, the development cost will depends on this.",
  },
  {
    question: "What if I need some changes in the website after the development process is complete?",
    answer: "Depending on the type of changes you need in your website or the services you choose; our committed team members answer your queries and support you accordingly. Furthermore, if you need any changes when the development process is still on or till the website hasn’t been launched, then just contact your development team directly for the same.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why to Choose Ftechiz for web development Services?",
    answer: "Ftechiz is one of the leading web development companies, with the highest customer satisfaction rate. There are various reasons why businesses are choosing Ftechiz for Web Development. The reasons usually vary from our Website Development services, Experience Developers, Industry Experience, Cost Effective Solutions, Client Satisfaction and latest technology stacks.",
  },
  {
    question: "Most of my Customers Use Mobile. Now What?",
    answer: "Our Responsive designs allow content of your website to flow smoothly across all screen sizes and resolutions with responsive design, and it will appear beautiful and same on all devices.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the most Popular programming Languages for Web Development in 2022?",
    answer: "Here is the list of some of the best and most popular programming languages used for website development in 2022: * React * Angular * PHP * Python * Angular * Java Script * Java * JS * .NET",
  },
];
export const hireremote_ques = [
  {
    question: "What is Ftechiz?",
    answer: "Ftechiz Solutions Pvt Ltd is one of the best software development company serving more than 10+ countries worldwide. We have 6+ years of tech expertise in app and web development, delivering 100+ projects since 2016. We have a team of 50+ IT experts consisting of developers, UI/UX designers, Testers, Project Managers & QA to ensure the smooth and successful delivery of your project.",
  },
  {
    question: "How to hire remote developers with Ftechiz?",
    answer: "You can conveniently hire remote developers with Ftechiz through our well-thought engagement models in 5-easy steps. Being best for any kind of short-term or long-term project, our remote developers are highly adaptive, and seamlessly gel in your environment while working in your preferred time zones. Once you’ve selected the developers, it’s time for contractual formalities, after which they will start working on your projects in the next 24 hours.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    You can hire remote developers as a valuable asset through the following easy steps:",
    answer1: "Step 1 – Tell us in brief about your ideas and needs",
    
    answer2: "Step 2 - Shortlist Candidates which best fit in your need by reviewing their CVs.",
    
    answer3: "Step 3 – Optionally, assess candidates over google meet, skype or any other medium.",
    
    answer4: "Step 4 – Take a 1-week free trial.",
    
    answer5: "Step 5 – If you like the resource(s), pay for the trial time and onboard resource(s).",
  },
  {
    question: "Is 7 days risk-free trial period completely free?",
    answer: "Yes, it's completely free. We allow this free trial period to evaluate the code quality, requirements, communication, on-time delivery, agile software development process, and more of the hired trial resource.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 If you like the resource, you can continue with the engagement; if the output isn't desired, we will assign new resource whose skills & experience match your requirement.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the cost to hire a remote Developer?",
    answer: "The average cost of hire a remote developer starts from $10 to $95/hour depending on the location. However, with companies like Ftechiz, you can hire remote developers for as low as $15/hour. Get in touch with our team to know the tailor-made costing structure for your business based on your requirements.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you ensure the security and confidentiality of our intellectual property?",
    answer: "Rest assured, you will have 100% ownership of your project. It includes NDA, copyright, source code, intellectual property rights, etc.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the most popular types of software development services I can expect from Ftechiz?",
    answer: "With year of experience in product development, project management, and UI/UX, we are a one-stop solution for any of your software development needs. Whether you need assistance with skilled resources or you are looking to outsource your project, you can rely upon us for; * Website development using emerging technologies * Mobile App development using cross-platform tools * Staff Augmentation – Fill the tech talent gap in your existing team * Full-stack Website development * Blockchain Development Services * Project Management * Post Launch Support",
  },
]
export const hireblockchain_ques = [
  {
    question: "Why should I hire Blockchain developers from Ftechiz?",
    answer: "Ftechiz have been in the market since 2016 and provide all kinds of services, from custom software development to hiring developers. We have: * 6+ years of experience * Delivered 50+ projects * Served 100+ customers * Expertise with the latest technologies",
  },
  {
    question: "Why should you invest in Blockchain development?",
    answer: "Some of the reasons why you should invest in developing Blockchain solutions are:- * Automation * Lower replication of data * Higher transparency * Faster transactions * Robust data security * Less data storage cost",
  },
  {
    question: "Which technology is best for developing a Blockchain app?",
    answer: "Here is the list of most important technologies used for developing Blockchain app: * Hyperledger * Ethereum * Stellar * Corda * EOS * Tron * Hashgraph * Ripple",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the business applications of Blockchain?",
    answer: "Here are some of the business applications of Blockchain Technology:- * Insurance * Real Estate * Supply Chain and Logistics * Media and Entertainment * Waste Management * Healthcare * Lending * Digital Identity * Government Operations",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I know your developers core strength and experience?",
    answer: "We have a pool of talented full-stack Blockchain developers who have years of experience working on top-notch and emerging technologies.",
  },
  {
    question: "What happen if developer doesn't perform well?",
    answer: "At any point of time of the running project, you can escalate the issue for non-performance. We would replace the resource within practically possible time with another resource.",
  },
  {
    question: "How would I be able to talk to the developers?",
    answer: "You can talk to developer  any time as per your convenience. You can use communications such as Email, Skype, Google Meet, Zoom, etc.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do You Have Expertise in Cloud?",
    answer: "Yes, we have a separate team with years of experience for cloud-based product and also for web & mobile app solution development. We will help you increase the proficiency and cost-effectiveness of the cloud services you use. Our expertise include: * AWS * Microsoft Azure * Google Cloud Platform",
  },
]
export const hirejava_ques = [
   {
    question: "Why should I Hire Java Developers from Ftechiz?",
    answer: "Ftechiz have been in the market since 2016 and provide all kinds of services, from custom software development to hiring dedicated java developers. If you want timely delivery of your project at low investment cost, it is a wise idea to opt for dedicated java developers who work solely on your project and deliver you faster results.  We have: * 6+ years of experience * Delivered 50+ projects * Served 100+ customers * Expertise with the latest technologies",
  },
  {
    question: "Will you replace the java developer if I am not satisfied with the performance?",
    answer: "Yes. We will definitely replace your developer if we see that there is any performance issue on the developer’s end.",
  },
  {
    question: "How Much Does It Cost To Hire Remote Java Developer?",
    answer: "The cost of hiring a Java developer may vary depending on many factors such as the time period of the project, expertise and experience requirements, location, complexity, etc. If you want to know the cost of your project, you can share your project idea, and we will provide you with an estimated cost of the project.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the business applications of Java?",
    answer: "Here are some of the business applications of Java:- * Insurance * Real Estate * Supply Chain and Logistics * Media and Entertainment * Waste Management * Healthcare * Lending * Digital Identity * Government Operations",
  },
  {
    question: "What About the Maintenance and Support after Project Development?",
    answer: "Yes, we provide all the maintenance and support after the project development if you need it. We are a full-service firm and our tech support executives are trained to handle the toughest of queries.",
  },
  {
    question: "How Can I Monitor and Analyse Developer Performances?",
    answer: "In Ftechiz, we allow you to conduct a thorough interview process for our developers and hire the dedicated developer of your choices.",
  },
]
export const hiremobile_ques = [
  {
    question: "Why should I hire Mobile App developers from Ftechiz?",
    answer: "In addition to delivering robust software solutions promptly, our mobile app developers bring several advantages, such as: * A pool of expert developers * Budget-friendly development * Best-in-class project management * Expertise with the latest technologies",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does a mobile app development cost?",
    answer: "The cost of a developing a mobile app depends on a various factors, including the complexity of the project, size, and number of developers, developer experience, and time required to complete the project, etc. You can share your project idea, and we will provide you with a cost estimate for your mobile app.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the security measures will you take to make my app idea secure?",
    answer: "To ensure the security of your app idea, we will sign an NDA (Non Disclosure Agreement) with you, providing the complete protection of your app idea.",
  },
  {
    question: "How many types of mobile apps do you develop?",
    answer: "Our team of mobile app developers has successfully developed a wide variety of apps from different business verticals like Healthcare, Entertainment, travel, finance, Real Estate, Fleet Management, Blockchain Wallet, business, to gaming and education apps.",
  },
  {
    question: "Will you assist your client in the app submission process?",
    answer: "Yes, of course! When you hire mobile app developer from us, you will get the development team who will upload your application on the App Store as an app development process. Our team has already uploaded over 50+ mobile apps successfully without charging any additional cost.",
  },
]
export const hirefullstack_ques = [
  {
    question: "Why should I hire Full Stack developers from Ftechiz?",
    answer: "Ftechiz have been in the market since 2016 and provide all kinds of services, from custom software development to hiring developers. We have: * 6+ years of experience * Delivered 50+ projects * Served 100+ customers * Expertise with the latest technologies",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost to hire full stack developers?",
    answer: "The cost to hire remote full stack developers tends to vary from one project to another. The cost depends upon various factors like project’s features & functionalities, total work hours required, the complexity of the project and a number of other factors.",
  },

  {
    question: "Which are the latest technologies used in Full Stack Web Development?",
    answer: "Here is the list of most important technologies used for Full Stack Web Development: * Front End Development: Angular Js, React Js, Vue Js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Typescript, JQuery * Back End Development: Node Js, PHP, .NET, Java, Python, Express Js, * Database Integration: MySQL, mongoDB, DynamoDB, Oracle,",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main advantage of using Full stack development services?",
    answer: "The main benefits of Full stack web development services are easy switching between front-end and back-end, working on the entire design structure at any level, saving costs, more secure, easy to upgrade, and others.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I know your developers core strength and experience?",
    answer: "We have a pool of talented full-stack developers who have years of experience working on top-notch and emerging technologies.",
  },
]